Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 2014-2015; Accession ARCH-2017-300
  - National Science Foundation, 3/19/2001 - 6/24/2015; G 3_19 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Government, 9/4/2014 - 5/15/2015; G 5 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - United Nations, UNESCO, 11/27/2000 - 6/10/2015; G 12 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - School of Medicine, 9/23/2014 - 4/29/2015; M 1 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - School of Medicine Departments, Miscellaneous, 4/16/2001 - 4/7/2015; M 5 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - SHC Administration, 9/19/2013 - 6/19/2015; SHS 3 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - SHC Board of Directors, 6/14/2013 - 3/4/2015; SHS 4 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital, 8/10/2001 - 5/4/2015; SHS 7 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Affiliated Hospitals, Centers Clinics, 7/7/2000 - 8/24/2015; SHS 13 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 11/2/2000 - 5/28/2015; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 6/11/2015 - 8/27/2015; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Education Groups/Organizations, 9/14/2000 - 8/12/2015; O 3 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 3/6/2015 - 8/3/2015; O 3_1 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - California Academy of Science, 9/5/2008 - 6/22/2015; O 3_2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - American Academy of Arts Sciences, 5/1/2001 - 1/22/2015; O 3_7 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - American Council on Education, 10/7/2014 - 7/14/2015; O 3_8 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NAICU, 10/3/2014 - 6/8/2015; O 3_10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The College Board, 2/10/2015 - 6/11/2015; O 3_25 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Aspen Institute, 1/26/2015 - 3/9/2015; O 3_37 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The National Academies, 4/10/2001 - 8/11/2015; O 3_43 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NCAA, 10/6/2014 - 6/30/2015; O 3_44 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pacific-12 Conference, 10/2/2014 - 5/26/2015; O 3_47 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Universities Colleges (1 of 3), 10/11/2000 - 10/11/2012; O 8 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Universities Colleges (2 of 3), 2/25/2013 - 5/26/2015; O 8 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Universities Colleges (3 of 3), 6/1/2015 - 8/27/2015; O 8 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Association of American Universities, 10/30/2013 - 6/8/2015; O 8_7 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - University of California, 7/30/2001 - 5/26/2015; O 8_43 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - University of Southern California, 9/4/2014 - 7/13/2015; O 8_49 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Western Association of Schools Colleges (WASC), 11/30/1999 - 3/25/2015; O 8_52 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Yale University, 12/19/2012 - 5/26/2015; O 8_53 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Inaugurations, 9/3/2014 - 8/31/2015; O 8_55 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 1/16/2015 - 4/21/2015; O 11 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - American Philosophical Society, 5/15/2001 - 4/25/2015; O 15 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Vice Provost and Dean of Research, 10/15/2013 - 5/15/2015; R 0 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Institute for Gender Research, 3/26/2002 - 10/27/2014; R 1_8 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Freeman Spogli Institute for International Studies, 2/12/2014 - 9/19/2014; R 1_12 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Students, Miscellaneous (1 of 3), 11/21/2000 - 3/9/2009; ST 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Students, Miscellaneous (2 of 3), 3/9/2009; ST 1 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Students, Miscellaneous (3 of 3), 9/10/2014 - 7/29/2015; ST 1 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Student Groups, Miscellaneous, 3/2/2001 - 5/19/2015; ST 1_1 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Gaieties, 8/23/2010 - 7/29/2015; ST 1_3 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), 10/31/2014 - 6/8/2015; ST 2 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Campus Compact, 10/2/2013 - 4/7/2015; ST 3_35 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 10/2/2000 - 8/4/2015; ST 8 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-303
  - Hennessy For President Poster (Box 1)
  - Gaities: Being John Hennessy Poster, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Publications with articles about Hennessy (Box 2)
  - Photographs - various (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - IEEE Honors, 2012 Jun 30 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, correspondence, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, correspondence, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, correspondence, 2000s (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bono: Ed Scott Event, 2002 Nov; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Presents 110th Commencement at Stanford (Fiorina), 2001 Jun 17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Interview of Dr. Joycelyn Elders, 2003 April; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Inauguration of John Hennessy as the Tenth President of Stanford University, 2000 Oct 20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - discover Stanford, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Penelope Maunsell Associates: Stanford Campaign for Undergraduate Education, 2001 May 2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - The Stanford Presidency: Conversations with Richard Lyman, Donald Kennedy, Gerhard Casper and John Hennessy, 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 4)
  - GSA Awards Dinner Celebration. "Pursuing Ingenuity: A Journey of Visionaries", 2010 Dec 9; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 4)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2018-032
  - Letters to undergraduate students, graduate students, and parents. (Box 1)